SKYLER THOMPSON

A Clinical Research Associate with five years of experience, specializing in ensuring compliance with GCP, FDA, and ICH regulations. A strong history of building strategic partnershipsand developing strategies to improve patient recruitment and retention.

123 Pine Brook Dr, Miami, FL 12345 sky I e rtho m pson@exa m ple.com (123) 456-7890

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

CLINICAL RESEARCH ASSOCIATE

Heart and Wellness Research Firm, Miami, FL September 2019 - Present

- Coo rd in ate with multidisciplinary research teams to execute clinical trials for cardiology research, including patient enrollment, qualification visits, and site initiation visits
- Define strategies for patient recruitment, build strategic partnerships with healthcare organizations, and develop new recruitment channels, resulting in a 120% increase in patient retention and a 50% reduction in associated recruitment costs
- Establish new documentation review protocols to ensure GCP regulatory compliance and reduce delays associated with IRB compliance by 40%

CLINICAL RESEARCH ASSOCIATE

St. John's Medical Center, Miami, FL May 2017 - September 2019

- Identified investigators, led patient recruitment initiatives, performed site initiatives visits (SIV),and conducted pre-study activities for oncology clinical research trials
- Managed preparation of documentation for IRB submissions and patient enrollment, including study protocols, consent forms, and confidentiality agreements

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science (B,SJ Clinical Research

University of Miami, Miami, FL September 2013- May 2017

KEY SKILLS

- Patient Recruitment
- ♦ Clinical Research Qualification
- ♦ Regulatory Compliance
- ♦ Clinical Studies
- ♦ GCP Regulations

CERTIFICATIONS

- Certified Clinical Research
 Professional (CCRP), SORCA, 2020
- Certified Clinical Research Associate (CCRA),ACRA, 2017